question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Television",
        "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "AMC's The Walking Dead, Rick, Carl, Daryl, Morgan, Carol and Maggie were introduced to us in Season 1.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The television show Doctor Who first aired in 1963.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the TV series Red Dwarf, Kryten's full name is Kryten 2X4B-523P.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Like his character in 'Parks and Recreation', Aziz Ansari was born in South Carolina.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Bob Ross was a US Air Force pilot.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injuried, and helpless.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In 'Star Trek', Klingons respect William Shakespeare, they even suspect him having a Klingon lineage.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In 'Star Trek', Klingons are commonly referred to as 'Black Elves'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In 'Star Trek: The Next Generation', Data is the only android in existence.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "An episode of 'The Simpsons' is dedicated to Moe Szyslak's bar rag.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
